

Personal details

Iheb Jabri

me.jabri.iheb@gmail.com

J +216 21241251

Tunisie, Béja, 9030 Amdoun

m July 9th, 1997

ට් Male

Tunisian

iheb.tn

linkedin.com/in/ihebjabri

Skills

Laravel /
Symfony / PHP

Ionic

Andriod
git / github / gitlab

Wordpress

Javascript /

Languages

Angular / Vue

English

French

Arabic

Iheb Jabri

Profile

I am an ambitious and hardworking person, with vast skills and experience in web development and mobile applications.

In addition, I am able to manage several daily tasks with competence and to work well under pressure.

A key strength is communication; build strong relationships with people in order to achieve the best results.

Recently, I obtained a higher technician diploma from the Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Béja and I am now fully employed by BluePen Labs as a Full Stack Developer.

Education

Senior technician

Sep 2017 - Jul 2020

Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Béja, Béja

Higher technician diploma at the Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Béja

Programming course

2017 - Present

Online

University courses were not enough for me to work, and I discovered this when I was looking for a freelance job, so most of what I acquired was online courses.

Bachelor 2013 - 2017

Bechir Sfar Secondary School, Amdoun

Bachelor- Degree in computer Science from Bechir Sfar Secondary School

Employment

Full Stack Developer

Nov 2020 - Present

BluePen Labs, Tunis

The cooperation with a team made up of various experiences has increased my experience in dealing with the problems that may be facing us and how to solve them with the best results.

Freelance

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Mostaql

Working as a freelance has added to me the property of mastering many programming languages and it is doubling my chances of obtaining a client in addition to mastering the work and obtaining customer satisfaction in order to obtain a good evaluation and feedback. other projects of this client.